Guide to the Simon Bauer papers,1932-2002.
Bauer, Simon papers, 1932-2002
  - #135. Structure of a Transient Dimer of Acetylene, S. H. Bauer and P. Jeffers, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 87, 3278 (1965). (Box 2)
  - #136. Optimized Geometry for Coupling a Mass Spectrometer to a Shock Tube, G. F. Marsters, S. H. Bauer, and E. L. Resler, Jr., 5th International Shock Tube Symp.; Proc. published by U. S. Naval Ord. Lab., Ed., Z. I. Slawsky (1966), Abs. C1, Bull. Am. Chem. Soc. 10, 1144 (1965). (Box 2)
  - #137. An Electron Diffraction Study of Trimethylsilyl iso-Thiocyanate and Trimethylsilyl isoCyanate, K. Kimura, K. Katada, and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 88, 420 (1966). (Box 2)
  - #138. Structures of C7H10, Valence Tautomers, as Determined by Electron Diffraction, J. F. Chiang and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 88, 416 (1966). (Box 2)
  - #139. The Role of Vibrational Excitation in H/D Exchange: Nascent Molecules at Room Temperature, S. H. Bauer, D. Marshall and T. Baer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 87, 5514 (1965). (Box 2)
  - #140. Decomposition of Cr(CO)6 in a Shock Wave, W. S. Watt and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 44, 2206 (1966). (Box 2)
  - #141. Isotope Exchange Rates. III. The Homogeneous 4-Center Reaction, H2 and D2, S. H. Bauer and Eugenio Ossa, J. Chem. Phys. 45, 434 (1966). (Box 2)
  - #142. Isotope Exchange Rates. IV. The Homogeneous Reaction Between CH4 and D2, W. S. Watt, Peter Borrell, D. Lewis and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 45, 444 (1966). (Box 2)
  - #143. An Electron Diffraction Study of the Structure of NF2 and N2 F4, R. K. Bohn and S. H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 6, 304 (1967). (Box 2)
  - #144. An Electron Diffraction Study of the Structures of cis and trans-Difluorodiazine, R. K. Bohn and S. H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 6, 309 (1967). (Box 2)
  - #145. The Molecular Structure of Perfluorodiazirine, J. L. Hencher and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 89, 5527 (1967). (Box 2)
  - #146. The Role of vibrational Excitation in Atom Switching Reactions, S. H. Bauer, AGARD Conf. Proc. No. 12, Recent Advances in Aerothermochemistry; Oslo, 1966, Vol. I, p.47, Ed., I. Glass (1967). (Box 2)
  - #147. Transient Species Generated During the Pyrolysis of Hydrocarbons, S. H. Bauer, 11th Symposium (International) on Combustion, Combustion Institute, Pittsburgh, 1967, p.105. (Box 2)
  - #148. The Structures of C6, B3 N3 and C3 N3 Ring Compounds, S. H. Bauer, K. Katada, and K. Kimura, Structural Chemistry and Molecular Biology, Eds., A. Rich and N. Davidson (1967), pp.681-697. (Box 2)
  - #149. An Electron Diffraction Study of KrF2 and Comments on the Structure of XeF6 W. Harshbarger and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 89, 6466 (1967). (Box 2)
  - #149a. Structures of XeF's QF3H3 (Kumura) (Box 2)
  - #150. The Molecular Structure of Trimethylenecyclopropane, E. A. Dorko, J. L. Hencher, and S. H. Bauer, Tetrahedron 24, 2425 (1968). (Box 2)
  - #151. The Structures of Norbornane and 1,4-Dichloronorbornane, J. Chiang, C. F. Wilcox, Jr., and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 90, 3149 (1968). (Box 2)
  - #152. On the Mechanism of H/D Exchange in the Homogeneous Reaction C2 H2+D2, at Intermediate Temperatures, S. H. Bauer, P. Jeffers, and N. Zevos, J. Phys. Chem. 71, 4412 (1967). (Box 2)
  - #152a. unpublished C2H2+C2O2 with P. Jeffers (1966). (Box 2)
  - #153. Revision of the Structure of SOF4, J. L. Hencher, D. W. J. Cruickshank, and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 48, 518 (1968). (Box 2)
  - #153a. ED Structure of Zr, Ha, Te Halides, J. V. Martinez, J. F. Chiang, and S. H. Bauer (1967) published) (Box 2)
  - #154. A Single-Pulse Shock Tube Study of the Pyrolysis of Perfluorocarbons and of the Oxidation of Perfluoroethylene, S. H. Bauer, K. C. Hou, and E. L. Resler, Jr., Proc. 6th International Shock Tube Symposium (May 1967), Berichte Ernest-Mach Institute (April 1968), Freiburg (1968), p.504: Abs. E7; Bull. Am. Chem. Soc. 13, 789 (1968). Phys. Fluids 12, (Suppl. 1), 125 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #155. Shock Front Structures A Chemical Kinetics View (Invited paper), 154th ACS Meeting (Sept. 1967), Division of Fuel Chemistry, Preprint Vol. 11, No. 4, pp.5981. (Box 2)
  - also: Kudriavtsev report: CO2 ? ? measurements (Box 2)
  - #156. Kinetics of the Nitrous OxideHydrogen Reaction, A Shock Tube Investigation, H. Henrici, M. Hunt, and S. H. Bauer. Presented 154th ACS Meeting, (Sept. 1967), Division of Fuel Chemistry, Preprint Vol. 11, No. 4. (Box 2)
  - #157. Book Review: The Characterization of High Temperature Vapors, Ed., J. L. Margrave, J. Wiley and Sons, 1967; American Scientist 56, No. 2, 164A (1968). (Box 2)
  - #158. Book Review: Stossrohre, H. Oertel, Springer-Verlag, New York, J. Am. Chem. Sac. 90, 4765 (1968). (Box 2)
  - #159. Structures and Conformations of the Cyclohexadienes, H. Oberhammer and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Sac. 91, 10 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #160. Isotope Exchange Rates. V. The Homogeneous Reactions Between H2S and D2, A. Burcat, A. Lifshitz, D. Lewis, and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 49, 1449 (1968). (Box 2)
  - #161. The Structure of Tricyclo[3,3,0216 ]octane, J. F. Chiang and S. H. Bauer, Trans. Faraday Soc. 64, 2247 (1968). (Box 2)
  - #162. The Structure of Borazine, W. Harshbarger, G. Lee, R. F. Porter, and S. H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 8, 1683 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #163. The Structure of Boroxine as Determined by Electron Diffraction, C. H. Chang, R. F. Porter, and S. H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 8, 1689 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #164. The Molecular Structure of 4-Chloronortricyclene, J. F. Chiang, C. F. Wilcox, Jr., and S. H. Bauer, Tetrahedron 25, 369 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #165. Isotope Exchange Processes VI. HD in Ar, D. Lewis and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Sac. 90, 5390 (1968). (Box 2)
  - #165a. The H2 + I2 reaction-with Ben W. (Box 2)
  - #166. Experimental Determination of Atom Form Factors at Small Scattering Angles, H. Oberhammer and S. H. Bauer, Bull. Am. Phys. Soc. 13, 834 (AT9) (1968). (Box 2)
  - #167. The Combustion of Hydrogen by Nitrous Oxide, H. Henrici and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 50, 1333 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #168. The Bimolecular Reaction of N20 with CO, and the Recombination of 0 with CO, as Studied in a Single Pulse Shock Tube, M. C. Lin and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 50, 3377 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #169. The Structure of B-Aminoborazine, W. Harshbarger, G. Lee, R. F. Porter, and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 91, 551 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #170. The Structure of (CH3)2 N4BH, C. H. Chang, R. F. Porter, and S. H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 8, 1677 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #171. Structure Of ClnSi(NCO)4n. A Study of Molecular Symmetry, R. L. Hilderbrandt and S. H. Bauer, J. Mol. Struct. 3, 325 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #171a. EO data on (F3C)On: 1,2,3 Hilderbandt (Box 2)
  - #172. The Structure of Cyclohexane; Conformation and Interatomic Distances, J. F. Chiang and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 91, 1898 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #173. Structure and Conformations of Perfluorohydrazine, M. Cardillo and S. H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 8, 2086 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #174. The Structure of Thiophene, 2-chloro and 2-bromothiophene, W. Harshbarger and S. H. Bauer, Acta Cryst. B26, 1010 (1970). (Box 2)
  - #175. The Variety of Structures Which Interest Chemists, S. H. Bauer, Chap. 1, Vol. IV, "Physical Chemistry, An Advanced Treatise", Academic Press, Ed., H. Eyring, et.al. (1970) p.741. (Box 2)
  - #176. Diffraction of Electrons by Gases, S. H. Bauer, Chap. 14, Vol. IV, "Physical Chemistry, An Advanced Treatise", Ed., H. Eyring, et.al., Academic Press, (1970) p.741. (Box 2)
  - #177. Operational Criteria for Concerted Bond Breaking in Gas Phase Molecular Elimination Reactions, S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 91, 3688 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #178. Studies of Conjugated Ring Hydrocarbons. The Structure of Dimethylfulvene, J. F. Chiang and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 92, 261 (1970). (Box 2)
  - #179. Reactions of F2O in Shock Waves. I. Kinetics and Mechanism of F2O Decomposition, M. C. Lin and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 91, 7737 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #180. Isotope Exchange Rates VII Homogeneous Atom Swi ching Between Oxygen Molecules VII, H. Carroll and ~S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 91, 7727 (1969). (Box 2)
  - #181. The Structure of Bicyclo[1,1,1]pentane, J. F. Chiang and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 92, 1614 (1970). (Box 2)
  - #182. The Molecular Structure of Perfluoroborodisilane, Si2 BF7 as Determined by Electron Diffraction, C. H. Chang, R. F. Porter and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 74, 1363 (1970). (Box 2)
  - #183. Bond Lengths and Bond Angles in the Sequence (CF3)2C=X, with X=O, NH, CH2, R. L. Hilderbrandt, A. Andreassen and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 74, 1586 (1970). (Box 2)
  - #184. Reactions of F2O in Shock Waves. II. Kinetics and Mechanism of the F2 O-CO Reaction, H. Henrici, M. C. Lin, and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 52, 5834 (1970). (Box 2)
  - #185. The Structure of Hexamethyl Dewar Benzene, M. J. Cardillo and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 92, 2399 (1970). (Box 2)
  - #186. Vibrationally Excited Methyl Chloride. I. The Rate of Production of CH2Cl*, T. Baer and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 92, 4769 (1970). (Box 2)
  - #187. Vibrationally Excited Methyl Chloride. II. Reactions of Vibrationally Hot but Translationally Cold CH2 Cl, T. Baer and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 92, 4773 (1970). (Box 2)
  - #188. Kinetics and Mechanism of the Reaction Between CO and SO,. Single Pulse Shock Tube Investigations, S. H. Bauer, P. Jeffers, A. Lifshitz, and B. P. Yadava, 13th Symposium on Combustion, The Combustion Institute, Pittsburgh, PA, (1971) p.417. (Box 2)
  - #189. Shock Synthesis of Amino Acids in Simulated Primitive Environments, A. BarNun, N. BarNun, S. H. Bauer, and C. Sagan, Science 168, 470 (1970). A longer version was published in Chemical Evolution and the origin of Life, Ed., Buret and Ponnamperuma. Patent # 3,652,434. (Box 2)
  - #190. The Structures of Azomethanes, C. H. Chang, R. F. Porter, and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 92, 5313 (1970). (Box 2)
  - #191. An Electron Diffraction Study of Perfluorocyclobutene and Perfluorocyclobutane, C. H. Chang, R. F. Porter, and S. H. Bauer, J. Mal. Struct. 7, 89 (1971). (Box 2)
  - #192. A Chemical CO Laser, M. C. Lin and S. H. Bauer, Chem. Phys. Lett. 7, 223 (1970). (Box 2)
  - #193. Structures of Strained Polycyclics: Bond Distances and Angles Bicyclo[2,1,1]hexene-2 and Tricyclo[3,3 0,0216]-oct-3-ene, D. L. Zebelman, S. H. Bauer, and J. F. Chiang, Tetrahedron 28, 2727 (1972). (Box 2)
  - #194. Chemical Dynamics, S. H. Bauer, 1971 Britannica Yearbook of Science and the Future, p.156. (Box 2)
  - #195. Mechanism of Production of CN at High Temperature in N2-C2H2 Mixtures, S. H. Bauer, A. BarNun and D. Lewis, Tech Report CU1PU to Project SQUID, June 1969 (33pp. + VII Tables and 20 Figures). (Box 2)
  - #196. The Structures of Perfluorobutyne-2 and Perfluorobutadiene-1,3, A. Andreassen, C. H. Chang, and S. H. Bauer, J. Org. Chem. 36, 920 (1971). (Box 3)
  - #197. Relaxation Processes at the Shock Front in CO2 Mixtures as Studied with a Laser-Schlieren Device, I. Hurle, M. Buchwald, and S. H. Bauer, Report distribution by the Laboratory of Plasma Studies of Cornell University (1970), (LPS# 51). (Box 3)
  - #198. The Structure of Hexafluoroacetylacetone and Hexafluoroacetic Anhydride, A. L. Andreassen, D. Zebelman, and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 93, 1148 (1971). (Box 3)
  - #199. The Reactions Between SO2 and C2H2(C2H4) at Elevated Temperatures: A Single Pulse Shock Tube Investigation, R. Fifer, R. Moreau, and S. H. Bauer, Int. J. Chem. Kin. 3, 249 (1971). (Box 3)
  - #200. The Structure of Bis(Trifluorophosphine)Diborane(4), Determined by Electron Diffraction, E. R. Lory, R. F. Porter, and S. H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 10, 1072 (1971). (Box 3)
  - #201. Comment: On the Structures of 2-chlorothiophene and 2-bromothiophene, R. R. Karl and S. H. Bauer, Acta Cryst. B28, 2619 (1972). (Box 3)
  - #202. Equilibrium Compositions at High Temperatures in Selected Mixtures of SO2,CO, Oxides of Nitrogen and Hydrocarbons, P. Jeffers and S. H. Bauer, Combustion & Flame 17, 432 (1971). (Box 3)
  - #203. The Structure of Perchlorocyclopropene, H. J. Mair and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 75, 1681 (1971). (Box 3)
  - #204. The Structure of Perfluorocyclopentene and Perchloropentadiene, C. H. Chang and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 75, 1685 (1971). (Box 3)
  - #205. Nucleation Study of Fe Vapor in Shock Tube Flow, R. T. V. Kung and S. H. Bauer, presented at 8th International Shock Tube Symposium, Proc. 8th Intnl. Shock Tube Symp., Ed., J. L. Stollery, Chapman and Hall (1971) paper #61. (Box 3)
  - #206(a) Chem kin in High T gases-von Karman? Lecture, May 1971 (Box 3)
  - #206(b) Recent Developments in Chemical Lasers, A Review, S. H. Bauer, Proc. Conf., IEEE, Cornell University (August, 1971) p.45. (Box 3)
  - #207. Reduction of Diffraction Data for Molecule with Large Amplitude Motions, The Structure of F3,CNO, S. H. Bauer and A. L. Andreassen, J. Phys. Chem. 76, 3099 (1972). (Box 3)
  - #208. The Molecular Structure of Trifluoromethyliodide and Homologues, A. L. Andreassen and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 56, 3802 (1972). (Box 3)
  - #209. Vibrational Relaxation of CO2, with Selected Collision Partners, I. H20 and D2O, M. Buchwald and S. H. Bauer, presented at 1971 Cambridge Symposium on Molecular Energy Transfer; J. Phys. Chem. 76, 3108 (1972). (Box 3)
  - #210. The Structures of Acetylacetone, Trifluoracetylacetone and Trifluoroacetone, A. L. Andreassen and S. H. Bauer, J. Mol. Struct. 12, 381 (1972). (Box 3)
  - #210a. Dimethioxymethane - ED structure, A. L. Andreassen & S. H. Bauer (Box 3)
  - #211. Vibrational Relaxation of CO2 with Selected Collision Partners. II. CH4, CD4, and CH3F, P. Walsh and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 77, 1078 (1973). (Box 3)
  - #212. Lasing Action and the Relative Populations of Vibrationally Excited CO Produced in Pulse-Discharged CS2 + 02 + He Mixtures, S. Tsuchiya, N. Nielsen, and S. H. Bauer, LPS Report #93, May 1972; J. Phys. Chem. 77, 2455 (1973). (Box 3)
  - #213. The Structure of Semibullvalene, Y. C. Wang and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 94, 5651 (1972). (Box 3)
  - #214. The Homogeneous Gas Phase H2-D2. Metathesis at Room Temperature: Reaction Induced by Specific vibrational Excitation, S. H. Bauer, D. M. Lederman, E. L. Resler, Jr., and E. R. Fisher, Int. J. Chem. Kin. 5, 93 (1973). (Box 3)
  - #215. The Structure of Bicyclo[2,1,0]Pentene, Determined by Electron Diffraction, J. F. Chiang, M. T. Kratus, A. L. Andreassen, and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Soc., Faraday Trans. 11 68, 1274 (1972). (Box 3)
  - #216. Chemical and Physical Processes Initiated in Ammonia by CO2, Laser Radiation, M. I. Buchwald, R. McFarlane and S. H. Bauer, presented at 3rd Conference on Chemical and molecular Lasers, St. Louis (May 1972) LPS Report #104. (Box 3)
  - #217. The Structures of Six Fluoroethylenes, J. Carlos, Jr., R. R. Karl, and S. H. Bauer, Trans. Faraday Soc. 11 70, 177 (1974). (Box 3)
  - #218. The Pyrolysis of Trimethylene Sulfide; A Unimolecular Decomposition, P. Jeffers, C. Dasch, and S. H. Bauer, Int. J. Chem. Kin. 5, 545 (1973). (Box 3)
  - #219. The Molecular Structure of Polysulphuryl Fluorides, S2 O5,F2, and S3,O8,F2, J. L. Hencher and S. H. Bauer, Can. J. Chem. 51(12), 2047 (1973). (Box 3)
  - #220. The High Temperature Reduction of Sulfur Dioxide by Hydrogen, R. Fifer, R. Moreau, and S. H. Bauer, Proceedings of 9th International Shock Tube Symposium, Ed., D. Bershader and W. Griffith, Stanford University Press (1973) p.731. (Box 3)
  - #221. SO2-Its Odyssey in a Combustion Chamber-A Review, S. H. Bauer, et.al., Preprint; Symposium on Combustion Chemistry, Div. of Petrol. Chem., Inc., Vol. 18, No. 2 (1973) p.307: 165th ACS Meeting (Box 3)
  - #222. The Molecular Structure of Closocarboranes (-5 and -6), E. A. McNeill, K. L. Gallaher, F. R. Scholer, and S. H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 12, 2108 (1973). (Box 3)
  - #223. Biphenylene: Internuclear Distances and Their Root Mean Square Amplitudes of vibration, A. Yokozeki, C. F. Wilcox, Jr., and S. H. Bauer, J. Am. Chem. Soc. 96, 1026 (1974). (Box 3)
  - #224. Pumping in H2: Estimate of Induced Dissociation at 300ºK, P. Jeffers, D. Hilden, and S. H. Bauer, Chem. Phys. Lett. 20, 525 (1973). (Box 3)
  - #225. The Gas Phase Structure of Tetramethylethylene, J. L. Carlos and S. H. Bauer, Trans. Faraday Soc., 11 70, 171 (1974). (Box 3)
  - #226. On the Thermochemical State of Gaseous Electron Diffraction Samples, K. L. Gallaher and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 78, 2380 (1974). (Box 3)
  - #227. Reinvestigation of the Structure of Perfluoroethane by Electron Diffraction, K. L. Gallaher A. Yokozeki, and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 78, 2389 (1974). (Box 3)
  - #228. The Relative Cis-Trans Isomerization Rates: A Test of the Dependence of k(E) on g(E), S. H. Bauer, B. P. Yadava, and P. Jeffers, J. Phys. Chem. 78, 770 (1974). (Box 3)
  - #228a. The Problem of Intramolecular Energy Redistribution (SHB--1974) qualitative (Box 3)
  - #229. The Homogeneous Pyrolysis of 2Butenes, P. Jeffers and S. H. Bauer, Int. J. Chem. Kin. 6, 763 (1974). (Box 3)
  - #230. The Gas Phase Structures of the Isomers of Benzene. II. Benzvalene, R. R. Karl and S. H. Bauer, J. Mol. Struct. 25, 1 (1975). (Box 3)
  - #231. The Gas Phase Structures of the Isomers of Benzene. III. Hexamethyl Prismane and Hexamethyl Benzene, R. R. Karl, Y. C. Wang, and S. H. Bauer, J. Mol. Struct. 25, 17 (1975). (Box 3)
  - #232. The Gas Phase Structures of the Isomers of Benzene. IV. HexafluoroDewar Benzene, K. Gallaher, Y. C. Wang, and S. H. Bauer, J. Mol. Struct. 25, 35 (1975). (Box 3)
  - #233. The Gas Phase Structures of Acetamide and Di-acetamide; Comment on the Effect of H-Bonding on the C-0 and C-N Bond Lengths, K.Gallaher and S. H. Bauer, Trans. Faraday Soc. 71, 1423 (1975). (Box 3)
  - #234. The Structures of Perfluoro-tert-butanol. A Monte-Carlo Integration for Three Concurrent Librators, A. Yokozeki and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 79, 155 (1975). (Box 3)
  - #235. The Effects of F for H Substitution on the Structures of Small Molecules, A Review, A. Yokozeki and S. H. Bauer, Forschrifte der Chemischen Forschung, Ed., F. Boschke, Topics in Current Chemistry 53, 71 (1975). (Box 3)
  - #236. Stimulated CO Emission of the (1-0) Band in a Pulse Initiated (CS2+O2,) Chemical Laser, J. Stricker and S. H. Bauer, Chem. Phys. Lett. 28, 98 (1974). (Box 3)
  - #237. Rate and Mechanism of Methane Pyrolysis from 2000º to 2700ºK, W. C. Gardiner, J. H. Owen, T. C. Clark, J. E. Dove, J. A. Miller, W. J. McLean and S. H. Bauer, presented at 15th Combustion Symposium (International), Tokyo, 1974, p.857. (Box 3)
  - #238. The Structure of 1,2,3,3-Tetrachloro-4,5 dimethyl spiro[2,3]-hexa-1,4-diene, K. Gallaher and S. H. Bauer, J. Mol. Struct. 28, 137 (1975). (Box 3)
  - #239. Infrared Laser Augmented Decomposition of H3,BPF3, E. R. Lory, T. Manuccia, and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 79, 545 (1975). (Box 3)
  - #240. The Structure of Thianthrene [(C6H4)2S2] Large Amplitude Motion in the Gas Phase, K. Gallaher and S. H. Bauer, Trans. Faraday Soc. 11 71, 1172 (1975). (Box 3)
  - Reports to ARO and ARPA (1972-1975) (Box 3)
  - #241. Laser Powered Homogeneous Pyrolysis-A Quantitative and Qualitative Kinetic Tool, W. Shaub and S. H. Bauer, Int. J. Chem. Kin. 7, 509 (1975). (Box 3)
  - Also: T1 distributions in irradiated cells (Box 3)
  - #241a. Flow and Temperature Fields of the Sample Gas in Laser-Powered Homogeneous Pyrolysis, (1986) (Box 3)
  - #242. The High Temperature oxidation of Methyl Mercaptan (Shock Waves), S. Matsuda and S. H. Bauer, Int. J. Chem. Kin., Symp. 1, 463 (1975). (Box 3)
  - #243. An Atomic Boron Laser, J. Stricker and S. H. Bauer, Chem. Phys. Lett. 30, 477 (1975). (Box 3)
  - Reports to AFOSR: Chemidium initiated by Co2 laser: Bar-Ziv (1976) (Box 3)
  - #244. The Structures of Dimethyl Disulfide and Ethyl Methyl Disulfide, A Yokozeki and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 80, 618 (1976). (Box 3)
  - #245. Development of a Computer Model for the (CH2,+O2) Chemical Laser: Documentation of Chemical Reactions and of Energy Transfer I Processes, N. Nielsen and S. H. Bauer, (UNPUBLISHED). (Box 3)
  - Ph.D Thesis (1975) (Box 3)
  - #246. Ensemble Constraints on the Dissociation Process in H2, and D2, S. H. Bauer, D. Hilden, and P. Jeffers, J. Phys. Chem. 80, 922 (1976). (Box 3)
  - #247. The Structure of Trifluoromethyl-Imino-Sulfurdifluoride, F3CN=SF2, R. R. Karl and S. H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 14, 1859 (1975). (Box 3)
  - #248. Relaxation Processes in H2-CO and D2-CO Mixtures from Fluorescence Induced by Stimulated Raman, H. Matsui, E. L. Resler, Jr., and S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Phys. 63, 4171 (1975). (Box 3)
  - #249. Chemical Lasers- USES, Encyclopedia of Chemical Tech, Florence (Italy), in Vol. 6 (1976). (In Italian) (Box 3)
  - #250. The Structure of (CF3,)3 CI, A. Yokozeki and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 80, 73 (1976). (Box 3)
  - #251. Homogeneous Nucleation in Metal Vapors: II. Dependence of the Heat of Condensation on Cluster Size, H. Freund and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 81, 994 (1977). (Box 3)
  - #252. Homogeneous Nucleation in Metal Vapors: V. A Self-Consistent Kinetic model, S. H. Bauer and D. J. Frurip, J. Phys. Chem. 81, 1015 (1977). (Box 3)
  - #253. Laser Augmented Decomposition II: D3BPF3K-R. Chien and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 80, 1405 (1976). (Box 3)
  - #254. Mass Spectrometric and Spectroscopic Study of the Reaction of H3BCO and B2H6 with Oxygen and Nitrogen Atoms, G. K. Anderson and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 81, 1146 (1977). (Box 3)
  - #255. The Combustion of Acetylene, and the REduction of NO Durinq the Combustion, W. M. Shaub and S. H. 35 (1977). (a) Disection of Ignition Delay Times via Laser Schlieren Measurements of Density Gradients at Shock Fronts, US.NTIS, AD/a, Rep 34 (1974). (Box 3)
  - #255a. Models for Combustion of C2H2-Destruction of NO2: Resler & Bauer (Box 3)
  - #256. Renaissance of Concern with the Nascent Condition, S. H. Bauer, J. Chem. Ed. 53, 372 (1976). (Box 3)
  - #256a. Molecular Structure of Sulfolane: Karl & Bauer (Box 3)
  - #257. Thermodynamic and Kinetic Parameters for Borane Exchanges, K-R. Chien and S. H. Bauer, Inorg. Chem. 16, 867 (1977). (Box 3)
  - #258. Homogeneous Nucleation in Metal Vapors, III. Temperature Dependence of the Critical Supersaturation Ratio of Fe, Bi and Pb, D. J. Frurip and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 81, 1001 (1977). (Box 3)
  - #259. Homogeneous Nucleation in Metal Vapors, IV. Growth Rate of Pb Clusters from Light Scattering, D. J. Frurip and S. H. Bauer, J. Phys. Chem. 81, 1007 (1977). (Box 3)
  - #260. The Molecular Dynamics Problem in Multiphoton Excitation, S. H. Bauer and K-R. Chien, Chem. Phys. Lett. 45, 529 (1977). (Box 3)
  - #261. How Energy Accumulation and Disposal Affect the Rates of Reations, S. H. Bauer, Chem. Rev. 78, 147 (1978). (Box 3)
  - #262. Proposed H/DT Separations Based on Laser Augmented A+B C Reactions, S. H. Bauer-ACS Symposium Series, #68 (1978) p.152. (Box 3)
  - #262a. Linear Inf vs <Eabs> for laser augmented RXus - SMB (1977) unpublished (Box 3)
  - #263. Visible Wavelength Chemiluminescence Initiated by CO2, Laser Radiation, S. H. Bauer, E. Bar-Ziv, and J. A. Haberman, U.S. NTIS, AD Rep. 31 (1976); IEEE-JQE QE-14, 237 (1978). (Box 3)
  - #264. Retention of Isotopic Selectivity During a Detonation; Laser Induced Reaction Between SF6, and SiH4, S. H. Bauer and J. A. Haberman, IEEE-JQE QE-14, 233 (1978). (Box 3)
  - #265. Stochastic Simulation of Homogeneous Condensation, S. H. Bauer, C. F. Wilcox, Jr., and S. Russo, J. Phys. Chem. 82, 59 (1978). (Box 3)
  - #266. Shock Tube Kinetics: Revitalized old Problems and Evolving New Ones, S. H. Bauer and D. K. Lewis, Proceedings: lith International Symposium on Shock Tubes and Waves, Eds., B. Ahlborn, A. Hertzberg and D. Russel, University of Washington Press, (1978) p.269. a Sol)) (Box 3)
  - #266a. Preparation of Hexamethylenetetramine from CH3OH/NH3 mixture via Laser-powered Homogeneous Pyrolysis, (1977) (Box 3)